somcloud.com 2016-11-04

# SomCloud - Privacy policy

    This privacy policy sets out how SomCloud uses and protects any information that you give SomCloud when you use our website, products and services.  
    
    SomCloud is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using SomCloud service, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.  
    
    SomCloud may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from March 30, 2012.

    Information Collection and use.

    We may collect the following information to provide with the best service.  
    
    - Personal information such as name, email address, contact information.  
    
    - Transactional information such as credit card number for upgraded products and services.  
    
    - Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests to improve our products and services.  
    
    You may elect to terminate your participation in the services at any time and/or delete information and material you have posted to any notebook.  
    
    You may also change your contact preferences after logging into your SomCloud account at www.somcloud.com and going to Preferences.

    Cookies and Tracking Pixels

    A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.   
    
    We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.   
    
    Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.   
    
    You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

    Links

    The SomCloud web site and services may contain links to other sites. SomCloud is not responsible for the privacy policy or other practices employed by web sites linked to, or from, our web site nor the information or content contained therein. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.

    Data Security

    We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.   
    
    We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

    Contact Us

    In using the SomCloud products and services you consent to the collection and use of this information by SomCloud. If you have questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy and out Terms of Service, please contact our customer services at support@somcloud.com
